<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>contract on Neatio | Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.neatio.net/tags/contract/</link>
    <description>Recent content in contract on Neatio | Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.neatio.net/tags/contract/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Neatio Tokenizes $NIO Coin on Polygon Network</title>
      <link>https://blog.neatio.net/post/neatio-polygon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.neatio.net/post/neatio-polygon/</guid>
      <description>Enhanced Efficiency and Speed ▸ Polygon Network Contract Address:: 0xaDD6f741Bc780b1b3633E05FceFed02047Cc84fA 0xaDD6f741Bc780b1b3633E05FceFed02047Cc84fA
▸ Introduction Exciting news has emerged in the crypto community, as the popular Neatio project has successfully migrated its tokenized version of the $NIO coin from the Binance Smart Chain to the Polygon network. The move comes as a strategic decision to enhance efficiency and speed in token transactions and further solidify Neatio&amp;rsquo;s position as a leading player in the decentralized finance (DeFi) space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Name History and Ticker Symbol</title>
      <link>https://blog.neatio.net/post/ticker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.neatio.net/post/ticker/</guid>
      <description>Choosing the right name for a project is essential, as it represents the vision, purpose, and identity of the endeavor. In the case of the Neatio project, the name itself carries a unique origin that reflects its core principles. Moreover, recognizing the importance of a professional and standardized approach, the project has recently undergone a change in its ticker symbol from NEAT to NIO, aligning it with renowned cryptocurrencies like BTC, ETH, SOL, ADA, and BNB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contract Migration and Ticker Change</title>
      <link>https://blog.neatio.net/post/neatio-contract/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.neatio.net/post/neatio-contract/</guid>
      <description>Neatio&amp;rsquo;s NEAT Token: Smart Contract Address Migration on the Binance Smart Chain network and new Neatio ticker &amp;ldquo;NIO&amp;rdquo; ▸ New wrapped NIO contract address: 0x9C8d7980fBaC17E1DdaE994Ce9Fe168c72eD5C37 ▸ Introduction In the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrency, projects often undergo updates and improvements to enhance their functionality and user experience. Neatio, a promising platform, is set to migrate its token &amp;ldquo;NEAT&amp;rdquo; to a new smart contract address on the Binance Smart Chain. This migration aims to remove the proxy admin contract and also change the token ticker to &amp;ldquo;NIO&amp;rdquo;, a more appropiate one for the Neatio name which for those of you who didn&amp;rsquo;t knew, the name Neatio is composed from &amp;ldquo;Neat&amp;rdquo; + &amp;ldquo;input output&amp;rdquo;, so we think &amp;ldquo;NIO&amp;rdquo; is the way to go.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
