<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Neatio | Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.neatio.net/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Neatio | Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.neatio.net/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project Name History and Ticker Symbol</title>
      <link>https://blog.neatio.net/post/ticker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.neatio.net/post/ticker/</guid>
      <description>Choosing the right name for a project is essential, as it represents the vision, purpose, and identity of the endeavor. In the case of the Neatio project, the name itself carries a unique origin that reflects its core principles. Moreover, recognizing the importance of a professional and standardized approach, the project has recently undergone a change in its ticker symbol from NEAT to NIO, aligning it with renowned cryptocurrencies like BTC, ETH, SOL, ADA, and BNB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contract Migration and Ticker Change</title>
      <link>https://blog.neatio.net/post/neatio-contract/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.neatio.net/post/neatio-contract/</guid>
      <description>Neatio&amp;rsquo;s NEAT Token: Smart Contract Address Migration on the Binance Smart Chain network and new Neatio ticker &amp;ldquo;NIO&amp;rdquo; ▸ New wrapped NIO contract address: 0x9C8d7980fBaC17E1DdaE994Ce9Fe168c72eD5C37 ▸ Introduction In the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrency, projects often undergo updates and improvements to enhance their functionality and user experience. Neatio, a promising platform, is set to migrate its token &amp;ldquo;NEAT&amp;rdquo; to a new smart contract address on the Binance Smart Chain. This migration aims to remove the proxy admin contract and also change the token ticker to &amp;ldquo;NIO&amp;rdquo;, a more appropiate one for the Neatio name which for those of you who didn&amp;rsquo;t knew, the name Neatio is composed from &amp;ldquo;Neat&amp;rdquo; + &amp;ldquo;input output&amp;rdquo;, so we think &amp;ldquo;NIO&amp;rdquo; is the way to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neatio&#39;s Off-Chain Governance</title>
      <link>https://blog.neatio.net/post/governance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.neatio.net/post/governance/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the Benefits of Decentralized Decision-Making In this blog post, we explore the unique features of Neatio&amp;rsquo;s off-chain governance system and its potential for decentralized decision-making. We also delve into Neatio&amp;rsquo;s first voting session, which presents two options with distinct advantages. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a Neatio token holder or simply interested in the evolving landscape of cryptocurrency governance, this post offers valuable insights into the power of decentralized decision-making.
▸ Introduction Neatio is a new cryptocurrency that has gained a significant amount of popularity in the digital currency market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Detailed Q1 2023 Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://blog.neatio.net/post/2023-roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.neatio.net/post/2023-roadmap/</guid>
      <description>In-depth Neatio project development milestones for the year 2023, quarter 1. ▸ Q1 2023 Roadmap The creation of a new roadmap for 2023 is an important step for the Neatio project as it sets the direction and priorities for the coming year. This roadmap will outline the major goals and objectives that the Neatio project aims to achieve in 2023, such as the development of new features, partnerships, and overall ecosystem development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neatio December Quest</title>
      <link>https://blog.neatio.net/post/december-quest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.neatio.net/post/december-quest/</guid>
      <description>111Today, we take a moment to celebrate our accomplishments and look forward to the future of Neatio project with a nice event dedicated to our community and supporters.
Over the past year, we have faced many challenges and overcome them, thanks to the hard work and dedication of our team and community. Today, we take a moment to celebrate our accomplishments and look forward to the future with a nice event dedicated to our community and supporters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neatio in a Nutshell</title>
      <link>https://blog.neatio.net/post/neatio-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.neatio.net/post/neatio-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Who we are? We are a team of software engineers and developers passionate about blockchain technology with a strong belief in the freedom and privacy of each individual. Our team is a perfect blend of core developers and UX/UI designers. We all love Bitcoin since it introduced us the amazing world of blockchain technology, we also love Ethereum and the smart contract technology but since both BTC and ETH became store of value rather than a peer-to-peer electronic cash system (like it was stated in the Bitcoin whitepaper by Satoshi Nakamoto) we decided to bring Neatio to life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
